

DAWIT SHIFETA

About Me

I'm a ambitious genius student who is fluent in two languages and has experience in web dev, 3d animation, video editing, forex trading, app dev.

i'm a hardworking man who doesn't give up until i achieve my goal or responsibility



+251911657167



Dshifeta2000@gmail.com



Addis ababa, bole bulbula

LANGUAGE

- English
- Amharic (basic)
- Spainish (beginner)

EXPERTISE

- Web development
- Creativity
- Digital Marketing
- 3d animation
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Good at everything tbh
- trading(unprofitable)

EXPERIENCE

3d animated intro for youtube channel

2020 - 2021

3d website for restraunt

2021 - 2022

Payment integrated web for cafe

2022 - 2023

Multiple logos for restaurants in

bulbula

2023 - 2024

EDUCATION

SOA

10th grade(currently) with 98.8 percentile in grade 8 nation test

Udacity-web design course

Web development course TJR bootcamp

SKILLS SUMMARY

Computing skill

Speaking skill

78 %

81 %